In the last couple of videos we have talked about code generation for simple
在最后几个视频中，我们已经讨论了简单的代码生成
programming language and I mentioned at the end of the last video that realistic
编程语言和我在上一个视频的末尾提到了逼真的
compilers do things a bit differently and in particular they do a better job of
编译器做事情的方式略有不同，尤其是它们在以下方面做得更好
keeping values and registers and of managing the temporaries that have to be
保存值和寄存器以及管理必须
stored in the activation record. We're actually going to talk about both of those
存储在激活记录中。我们实际上要讨论这两个问题
problems. In this particular video, we're only going to talk about the second one
问题。在这段特别的视频中，我们只讨论第二个
and so we're going to be covering a better ways for compilers to manage temporary
因此，我们将介绍一种更好的方法，让编译器管理临时
values. So the biggest idea which we've already seen is to keep temporaries in the
价值。所以我们已经看到的最大的想法是在
activation record. Now, this is not as efficient as keeping temporaries in
激活记录。现在，这比不上把临时人员放在
registers but that's the subject of a future video, we're not going to talk
但这是未来视频的主题，我们不会谈论
about that today. What we're going to talk about is improving the language we manage
关于今天的事。我们将要谈论的是改进我们管理的语言
temporaries that happened to be in the activation record for whatever reasons. So
无论出于什么原因碰巧出现在激活记录中的临时文件。所以
why, it doesn't matter why we want them to be into activation record, but given that
为什么，我们为什么想让他们进入激活记录并不重要，但是考虑到
it's there, that's the most efficient code that we can generate And, the improvement
它就在那里，这是我们能生成的最有效的代码，而且，改进
that we're going to make Is have the co-generator assign a fixed location In
我们要做的是让联合发电机在
the activation record for each temporaries. We're going to pre-allocate
每个临时的激活记录。我们要预先分配
memory or a spot in the activation record for each temporary and then we will be
内存或激活记录中的一个点，然后我们就会
able to save and restore the temporary without having to do the stack pointer
无需使用堆栈指针即可保存和恢复临时
manipulations. So, let's take a look at the [inaudible] program for a simple
操纵。那么，让我们看一看简单的[听不见的]节目
programming language. Here is the Fibonacci function again and let me change
编程语言。这里又是斐波纳契函数，让我修改一下
colors to something that says more contrast and let's think about how many
用颜色来表示更强的对比度，让我们想一想有多少
temporaries we need to evaluate this functions. So, this function body when it
临时的，我们需要评估这个函数。因此，此函数体在其
executes we'll need a certain number of temporaries and if we know how many
我们需要一定数量的临时人员，如果我们知道有多少
temporaries that needs in advance then we could allocate the space for those in the
那么我们就可以分配空间给那些在
activation record rather having to do push and pop, pushing and popping from the
激活记录，而不是必须推送和弹出，推送和弹出从
stack at runtime. So, let's take a look and if then else is going t o involve a
在运行时堆栈。所以，让我们来看一下，如果这样的话会不会涉及到
temporary because it always do this predicate comparison here, we're going to
临时的，因为它总是在这里执行谓词比较，所以我们将
have to evaluate the, the first argument to the predicate and then save the result
我必须计算谓词的第一个参数，然后保存结果
of that while we evaluate the second argument to the predicate. So this one
当我们计算谓词的第二个参数时。所以这个人
involve one temporary, we'll need one temporary for that predicate. Similarly
涉及一个临时的，我们需要一个临时的谓词。同样，
for this predicate, to evaluate it since it's a two argument operation in
对于此谓词，要对其求值，因为它是
comparison, we'll also need one temporary for that. 1010. There's this expression
比较一下，我们还需要一辆临时的。1010号。有这样一种表达方式
over here which is kind of complicated. How many temporaries will we need for
在这里，这有点复杂。我们需要多少临时人员呢？
these? Well, remember how this works. So, evaluate the first expression and then we
这些?嗯，记住这是怎么回事。因此，计算第一个表达式，然后我们
save the results of that so this will require one temporary for the result of
保存该结果，因此这将需要一个临时的
the called fib going to have to be saved and only evaluate the plus And while we
必须保存被调用的fib，并且只计算加号和While
are evaluating the call, the fib though is actually, before we evaluate to call the
正在评估调用，但实际上，在我们评估调用
fib, we have to evaluate the argument of fib and that involve the subtractions. We
我们要计算fib的论点，涉及减法。我们
also need one temporary here for the subtraction. Okay And now we have about
这里也需要一个临时的来做减法。好的，现在我们有大约
the second side of the, this edition here. Well this also involves a subtraction.
第二面，这个版本在这里。这也涉及到减法。
Okay So, we got to have one temporary here to hold on to the value x while we're
好的，所以，我们在这里有一个临时的，当我们在这里的时候，我们可以保持x的值。
evaluating the minus to compute the value of the argument before we call
在调用之前计算减号以计算参数的值
[inaudible]. Okay? So how many temporaries do we need in total? While we need one
[听不见]。好吧?那么我们总共需要多少临时人员呢？当我们需要一个的时候
here for the predicate, but notice that once the predicate is decided, once we
这里是谓词，但是请注意，一旦决定了谓词，一旦我们
know the answer to whether this predicate is true or false, we don't need that
知道这个谓词是真是假的答案，我们不需要这个
temporary anymore. So in fact, that temporary can be reclaimed; we don't need
不再是暂时的了。所以事实上，临时的是可以回收的；我们不需要
the space for that temporary anymore by the time we get to the false branch. And
当我们到达错误的分支时，暂时的空间就不再存在了。和
again, once this predicate is evaluated, we don't need the space for that temporary
同样，一旦评估了这个谓词，我们就不需要临时的空间了
anymore, okay? So now we're down to the plus. The first thing that happens is we
再也不会了，好吗？所以现在我们要降到正数了。发生的第一件事就是我们
evaluate the argument to this first call the fib. Once that's evaluated, we don't
对此第一个调用fib的参数求值。一旦评估过了，我们就不会
need the temporary for it anymore. Now the results of fib has to be saved somewhere
再也不需要临时的了。现在，fib的结果必须保存在某个地方
while we do the plus, okay? And then we'r e going to have to evaluate the argument
我们做加法的时候，好吗？然后我们将不得不对论点进行评估
to the second call of fib and then notice that this happens while we still need this
到第二个fib调用，然后请注意，这发生在我们仍然需要它的时候。
temporary here so in fact, we need both of these temporaries at the same time. Okay
这里是临时的，所以事实上，我们同时需要这两个临时的。好吧
because while we're evaluating this argument, the second call of fib, we still
因为当我们评估这个论点的时候，第二次说谎，我们仍然
need to be holding on to the first argument to the plus. And so in fact this
需要坚持加号的第一个论点。所以事实上这是
particular function can be evaluated with just two temporaries. So all the space we
只需两个临时函数就可以评估特定的功能。所以我们所有的空间
need to compute the value of this function body. So in general, we can define a
需要计算此函数体的值。因此，一般而言，我们可以定义一个
function nt of e that computes a number of temporaries  needed to evaluate e1 + e2.
e的函数nt，它计算计算e1+e2所需的时间数。
So, that's going to need at least as many temporaries as e1. Okay, so if we need a
所以，这至少需要和E1一样多的临时时间。好的，所以如果我们需要一个
number of temporary's k to evaluate e1, let's have at least k temporaries to
计算E1的临时数k，让我们至少有k个临时数
evaluate the whole expression And then, we'll also need at least as many
计算整个表达式，然后，我们还需要至少
temporaries as it's needed to evaluate the two+1 because we have to hold on to the
因为评估2+1是必要的，因为我们必须坚持
value of e2 while we are evaluating so we have to hold on the value of e1 while
e2的值，所以我们必须保持e1的值，而
we're evaluating the two. Okay And it's going to be the maximum. Over these two so
我们正在评估这两个人。好的，这将是最大的。在这两个上面，所以
it'll be the maximum number with between the maximum number of temporaries need to
这将是介于需要的最大临时数量之间的最大数量
evaluate a one and one + the number of temporaries to evaluate two. That would be
求1和1+临时数来求2。那就是
the total number of temporaries, the minimum number of temporaries needed to
临时人员总数，满足以下要求的最小临时人员数量
evaluate e1 + e2 And the reason is a max instead of a sum. Is that once we've
计算e1+e2，原因是最大值而不是总和。一旦我们
evaluate e1 we don't need any of the space that was used to evaluate e1 anymore. All
求值，我们不再需要任何用来求值的空间。全
those temporaries are done. All we need is the answer. We don't need the immediate
那些临时的已经做完了。我们需要的只是答案。我们不需要即刻的
results and that means that the temporaries that were used to evaluate e1
结果这意味着用来评估E1的颞叶
can be reused to evaluate e2. So, generalizing from that one example, here
可以重用来评估e2。所以，从这个例子来概括一下，这里
is the system of equations that subscribes the number of temporaries needed to
是订阅所需时间的方程式系统
evaluate every kind of expression in our little language. So, let's take a look.
用我们的小语言评估每一种表达方式。那么，我们来看一看。
So, we already talked about e1+e2 is just the max of over the number or temporaries
所以，我们已经讨论过，e1+e2就是超过一个或多个临时数的最大值
to value of e1 and one + number of temporaries to value of e2. So, e1-e2 is
设置为e1的值，并将1+个临时数设置为e2的值。因此，e1-e2是
exactly the same thing because the same structure is a different computational
完全相同的事情，因为相同的结构是不同的计算
operation but is a binary operation and we have to save the value of e1 while
运算，但这是一个二进制运算，我们必须保存e1的值，而
evaluated e2. So, it's the same formula. [inaudible] Now for if and else well what
评估e2。所以，这是相同的公式。[听不见]现在是如果，否则会怎么样？
do we need? We need one, I'm sorry we need, it's going to max again. It's going
我们需要吗？我们需要一辆，很抱歉我们需要，它又要开到最高了。它要走了
to be max over some number of different quantities. How many temporaries might we
在某一数量的不同数量上取最大值。我们可能会有多少个临时工
need? Well, we might need as many temporaries or as needed to evaluate the
需要吗？嗯，我们可能需要尽可能多的临时工或根据需要来评估
value of e1 and we certainly need at least as many, alright. So, if you want to take
E1的值，我们当然需要至少同样多的，对吧。所以，如果你想带上
a certain number of temporaries, the whole f and l is going to require at least as
一定数量的临时函数，整个f和l将需要至少
many temporaries. Now of course, once e1 is done evaluating, we don't need its
很多临时工。当然，一旦E1完成评估，我们就不需要它
temporaries anymore. And, and we can evaluate e2, okay. And while we are
不再是临时的了。然后，我们可以评估e2，好的。当我们在这里的时候
evaluating e2, we have to hold on. To the results of e1, that's where the one plus
评估e2，我们必须坚持住。对于E1的结果，这就是一加
comes from. So, to that, while we're evaluating e2, we need one plus the number
来自于。因此，当我们计算e2时，我们需要1加上数字
of temporaries to evaluating two to hold all the temporaries of the computation.
计算两个以容纳计算的所有时间。
And then once the predicate is done, we don't need any of those temporaries
一旦谓词完成，我们就不需要任何这些临时语句了
anymore at all ad we're going to evaluate either e3 or e4. And so then, we just need
再说，我们要计算E3或E4的值。因此，我们只需要
however many temporaries each of those requires and whatever the maximum is over
不管每一个需要多少临时时间，不管最大值是多少
these four quantities, that's the minimum number of temporaries we can get away with
这四个数量，这是我们能逃脱的最小临时数量
to evaluate the entire if then else. Let's take a look at a function call. So that
来评估整个IF THEN ELSE。让我们来看一下函数调用。所以
the space needed for the function call is number of temporaries, the max over the
函数调用所需的空间是临时数，最大值超过
number of temporaries to evaluate anyone of the arguments and this is actually an
计算任何参数的临时数，这实际上是一个
interesting case because notice. That we don't need, we don't have anywhere in this
有趣的案例因为注意到。我们不需要的东西，我们在这里没有任何地方
formula space for the results for the e1 through en Of course once we've evaluated
公式空间用于E1到EN的结果，当然，一旦我们进行了评估
the e1 then we need to save it somewhere and so you would think that we might see
那么我们需要把它保存在某个地方，所以你会认为我们可能会看到
some numbers in here representing the temporary space needed to hold on to the
这里的一些数字表示需要保留的临时空间
results of the evaluating these expressions. And the reason that we don't
计算这些表达式的结果。我们之所以不这么做
have that in here is that. Even though those values are saved, they are indeed
把它放在这里就是这样。即使保存了这些值，它们也确实
saved; they're not saved in the current activation record The space where the
已保存；它们未保存在当前激活记录中
results of e1 and the results of all, any of the arguments. Yeah, again, is saved in
E1的结果和所有、任意参数的结果。是的，再一次，被保存在
the new activation record that we're building And so, the space for the, the
我们正在构建的新激活记录，因此，
results of e1 through en is that those values are stored in new activation record
E1到EN的结果是这些值存储在新的激活记录中
and that storage of current activation record and we're trying to compute the
以及当前激活记录的存储，我们正在尝试计算
number of temporaries needed to evaluate inside of the current activation And then
当前激活内部需要评估的临时数，然后
for integer, that doesn't take any space at all to require any temporaries I mean.
对于整数，我的意思是不需要任何空间就需要任何临时函数。
So there's zero temporaries required for that and also for a variable reference so
所以不需要任何临时函数，也不需要变量引用，所以
it requires no temporaries. So now let's go through our example and work out
它不需要临时的东西。现在让我们来看一下我们的示例，并计算出
systematically using the equations. How many temporaries we will need? Okay? So,
系统地使用这些方程。我们需要多少临时人员？好吧?所以,
here for this if then else, remember it was going to be the max over the number
在这里，如果是这样的话，记住它将是最大值除以这个数字
required to evaluate e1, well that zero. One + the number to evaluate e2 which is
需要对E1求值，很好地说是零。1+评估e2的数字，该数字为
the second expression in the predicate so that would be one, because the number one
谓词中的第二个表达式是1，因为数字1
requires zero temporaries and the one, the we have one hold on to x, all right? And
需要零时间和一，我们只有一次抓住x，好吗？和
then max over the branches. So, to evaluate zero requires Zero temporaries
然后最大限度地越过树枝。因此，计算零需要零时态
and now. We have to compute. The number required here. Okay so once again to
现在呢。我们必须进行计算。这里需要的号码。好的，再来一次
evaluate the first expression if and else requires zero temporaries to evaluate the
计算第一个表达式IF和ELSE需要零个时态才能计算
second one we require one. One + the number required, one + zero to evaluate
第二个我们需要一个。1+所需数字，1+0评估
that constant we got zero temporaries and now for the last expression how many will
这个常数，我们得到了零个时间，现在最后一个表达式有多少个
this one will require. Well this is going to require zero for this guy. One for the
这一次需要。这对这个人来说需要零。一个用于
second argument so to evaluate fib is going to require one temporary, okay and
第二个参数，所以计算fib需要一个临时的，好的，
then it's going to be one plus over here. We have to hold on to the results there.
那么这里就加一分了。我们必须坚持那里的结果。
The value of x - two so how much that going to require? That is going to require
x-2的值，那么需要多少钱呢？这将需要
the max of zero and one + zero okay so this would be one alright so we have over
最大0和1+0，好的，这是1，好的，我们结束了
here we have one + one = two okay and now we're taking the max over two and one. So
这里我们有1+1=2，好的，现在我们取最大值除以2和1。所以
that's two, okay? And this is the last expression in the, our if and else. So
那是两个，好吗？这是，我们的if和Else中的最后一个表达式。所以
clearly, this if then else here will require two temporaries okay? Because the
很明显，如果是这样的话，这里需要两个临时的时间，好吗？因为
max over the number required for either part of the predicate, the then branch and
最大值超过谓词的任一部分所需的数量，即THEN分支和
the else branch And now, this whole expression. Requires two temporaries and
Else分支，现在，整个表达式。需要两个临时的和
that'll be the max of the four components of the outer if then else And so then for,
这将是外部If Then和Else的四个分量中的最大值，
for the entire expression we get two temporaries. Once it computed the number
对于整个表达式，我们得到两个临时表达式。一旦它计算出这个数字
of temporaries required to evaluate the function value, we can add that much space
计算函数值所需的时间，我们可以添加这么多空间
to the activation record. So, now our activation record is going to require two
添加到激活记录中。所以，现在我们的激活记录将需要两个
+ n + nt (e) elements And so, the two of course are for the return address for the
+n+nt(E)元素，因此，这两个元素当然是
frame pointer. The n is for the n argument of the function And then, the rest of it
帧指针。n表示函数的n自变量，然后是函数的睡觉
is just the space required for the temporaries And now we can talk about how
只是临时建筑所需的空间，现在我们可以谈谈
we're going to layout the activation record. We'll leave the first part of it
我们要布置激活记录。我们把它的第一部分留下来
the same, so everything up to the return address is laid out just before. First the
相同的，所以直到寄信人地址的所有东西都是在前面布置的。首先是
color string pointer then the and arguments in reverse order, and then the
颜色字符串指针，然后按相反顺序显示和参数，然后是
return address. And then after the return address come the and locations or the
回邮地址。然后在返回地址之后是和位置或
nt(e), excuse me, locations for the temporaries.
NT(E)，打扰一下，临时人员的位置。